Dad.
I want you to break the contract right now
and give my dad back his chance to reincarnate.
I can't do that.
Why?
Why can't you?
It's not that I don't want to,
but I have no way to wake him up either.
Then let's start over again.
Let everything go back to the beginning.
I'll pretend I never met you.
Even if time turns back,
an injured soul
cannot be restored.
You are a murderer.
You've been one for a thousand years.
You'll do anything to achieve your goals.
At first, I didn't know your identities in your past lives.
In your eyes,
can the soul of an insignificant person
be taken away by you at will?
No, listen to me.
Enough.
Selfishness is your nature.
It's been deeply rooted in your soul for a long time.
The reason you act like this
is nothing more than to make up for your hypocritical guilt.
It's really terrifying.
What exactly did my dad and I do wrong
to have to meet you in every lifetime?
I'm begging you.
Let me go.
Let my dad go.
Can you?
Stop acting like an evil spirit
and pestering us, okay?
What brings you here?
You rascal.
This is nonsense.
Is there any other way?
A way?
There is one.
But the price is a bit high.
What is it?
You must inject your soul power
into the other person.
Until your soul dissipates
and turns to dust.
If it were you,
what would you do?
That depends
on what you are doing this for.
Please annul our engagement
and set me free.
It's because of that man.
Do you really think he is sincere to you?
Don't be silly.
Do you know who he is?
He is the First Prince.
He is the culprit who caused your father's death.
Impossible.
When the two armies were at war,
the First Prince deserted out of fear of the slaughter,
causing the frontline to lose morale.
In the end, it was your father
who took the blame for him.
You actually had the delusion
of eloping with him.
How ridiculous.
Think about it.
Haven't you always wanted to avenge your father and clear his name?
Now you have the chance.
Kill him.
Then you can avenge your father.
I will immediately break off our engagement and set you free.
Think it through yourself.
An abandoned prince.
Why kill him?
No.
Only if he dies
can the Second Prince be at ease.
Why?
Murderer.
Tang'er.
Mafeisan.
This blade severs all grudges and affections.
From now on, we are strangers.
Miss Tang'er.
How did it go?
From now on,
I have nothing to do with Prince Ling's Mansion.
We owe each other nothing.
This female thief assassinated the prince.
Kill her without mercy.
I expected this.
Stop.
Tang'er.
Chenyao.
Kill him.
Your Highness.
Let me explain.
It... It's her.
She killed you.
I was helping you get rid of this traitor.
I deserve to die.
It's the Second Prince.
Tang'er.
It's all because of me
that you and your father suffered.
Maybe...
I'm just trying to atone for my sins.
Who asked you to atone?
It's been lifetimes.
Why are you still clinging to the past?
You need to learn to let go,
look forward to things,
feel the present with your heart,
and bravely embrace the beauty of the future.
Can I really let go?
Of course.
Think about it.
You're only a few years away from a thousand years of service.
Is it worth it?
Given our relationship,
I'll ask the higher-ups
and get you
a more relaxing position, okay?
I've figured it out.
Exactly. Isn't that better?
Go on.
Remember, don't come empty-handed next time.
This kid.
Wait a minute.
If he's still clinging to the past,
why did he grab that key?
Mr. Gu.
I just got news from the private investigator.
They said they found Mu Chen and Hao Zhenshi.
Where are they?
The message says they're in an abandoned building.
Let's go then.
We don't have time.
The trial is about to start.
Call the police.
We can't call the police.
I thought about calling the police too.
But I'm afraid the police will provoke him.
He might resort to extreme measures
and take everyone down with him.
Then what do you suggest?
There's only one way now.
Let Chen Yao go.
Him?
He can't go.
What?
Where did he go?
I... I don't know.
Did something happen between you two?
Lawyer Gu.
At a critical moment like this,
are we going to fail at the last minute?
Hurry up and find him to bring him back.
Where am I supposed to find him?
What are you hesitating for?
You know how cunning Ling Hengsheng is.
This is our only chance.
I got it.
What do you know?
Then tell me who should go.
The police?
Or you?
I'll go.
Brother Chen.
I'm glad you're here.
Don't yell at her again.
Yes.
I was just too anxious.
I found a way to wake your father up.
When all this is over,
I will definitely wake him up.
Give me the address.
You guys head to the court first.
Okay.